{
  "new_questions": [
    {
      "question": "What are deposits made under EQ Bank and Equitable Bank eligible for?",
      "answer": "EQ Bank is a trademark of Equitable Bank. Yes\u2014deposits made under EQ Bank and Equitable Bank are aggregately eligible for CDIC protection up to $100,000, per insured category, per depositor, as outlined in CDIC\u2019s \" Eligible deposits in your joint account are insured separately.",
      "score": 10.725418090820312
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the maximum amount of protection paid by the CDIC?",
      "answer": "Equitable Bank is a member of the CDIC. \u201d Enter the dollar value of the cheque in the \u201cAmount\u201d field, then select the account you wish to deposit the funds into. Paid (T4E)",
      "score": -3.8018431663513184
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Protecting Your Deposits?",
      "answer": "Protecting Your Deposits\". The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": -0.022939741611480713
    },
    {
      "question": "What does Protect Your Deposit?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Although the deposit is reflected immediately in your account balance, you won\u2019t be able to withdraw or transfer your funds until the hold period has passed. Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": 3.0806779861450195
    },
    {
      "question": "How much are you covered for?",
      "answer": "Banks are required to report the interest you earn each year to the Canada Revenue Agency. For example, you\u2019re covered for up to $100,000 combined across your individual Savings Plus Account, EQ Bank GICs, and any deposits in your name that you have with Equitable Bank. Eligible deposits in your joint account are insured separately.",
      "score": 12.13899040222168
    },
    {
      "question": "How much is the combined amount of your savings account?",
      "answer": "EQ Bank offer a high-interest savings account (Savings Plus Account), TFSA Savings Account, RSP Savings Account, and GICs (guaranteed investment certificates). \u201d Enter the dollar value of the cheque in the \u201cAmount\u201d field, then select the account you wish to deposit the funds into. The Savings Plus Account is for personal use only.",
      "score": -1.873026728630066
    },
    {
      "question": "What are eligible deposits in your joint account insured separately?",
      "answer": "Protecting Your Deposits\". Yes\u2014deposits made under EQ Bank and Equitable Bank are aggregately eligible for CDIC protection up to $100,000, per insured category, per depositor, as outlined in CDIC\u2019s \" Eligible deposits in your joint account are insured separately.",
      "score": 1.7973625659942627
    },
    {
      "question": "What is EQ Bank a trademark of?",
      "answer": "EQ Bank is a trademark of Equitable Bank. EQ Bank is the digital arm of Equitable Bank. Based in Toronto, EQ Bank is a trademark of Equitable Bank.",
      "score": 15.285713195800781
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is a member of the CDIC?",
      "answer": "Equitable Bank is a member of the CDIC. EQ Bank is the digital arm of Equitable Bank. Yes\u2014deposits made under EQ Bank and Equitable Bank are aggregately eligible for CDIC protection up to $100,000, per insured category, per depositor, as outlined in CDIC\u2019s \"",
      "score": 13.277250289916992
    },
    {
      "question": "How long does EQ Bank hold funds deposited by cheque or Electronic Funds Transfer?",
      "answer": "Generally, EQ Bank hold funds deposited by cheque or Electronic Funds Transfer (EFT) for five business days, beginning after the date of deposit. Although the deposit is reflected immediately in your account balance, you won\u2019t be able to withdraw or transfer your funds until the hold period has passed. For more details, check out our Hold Funds Policy.",
      "score": 10.88961410522461
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the term for EFT?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Generally, EQ Bank hold funds deposited by cheque or Electronic Funds Transfer (EFT) for five business days, beginning after the date of deposit. The Savings Plus Account is for personal use only.",
      "score": 16.797443389892578
    },
    {
      "question": "How many business days will funds held become available?",
      "answer": "Please note: EQ Bank is not available in Quebec. Generally, EQ Bank hold funds deposited by cheque or Electronic Funds Transfer (EFT) for five business days, beginning after the date of deposit. This means that funds held will actually become available by the sixth business day, when you include the date of deposit.",
      "score": 11.476224899291992
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the date of the deposit?",
      "answer": "Take a photo of both the front and back of the cheque, then click \u201cDeposit. \u201d Enter the dollar value of the cheque in the \u201cAmount\u201d field, then select the account you wish to deposit the funds into. This means that funds held will actually become available by the sixth business day, when you include the date of deposit.",
      "score": 6.942492485046387
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of deposit can you make on a Monday?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. For example, if you make a deposit on a Monday, you can access the funds on the following Tuesday. In the bottom right corner, click on \u201cDeposit.",
      "score": -2.174328327178955
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the day you make a deposit?",
      "answer": "For example, if you make a deposit on a Monday, you can access the funds on the following Tuesday. \u201d Enter the dollar value of the cheque in the \u201cAmount\u201d field, then select the account you wish to deposit the funds into. This means that funds held will actually become available by the sixth business day, when you include the date of deposit.",
      "score": 13.407115936279297
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the deposit reflected in your account balance?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. \u201d Enter the dollar value of the cheque in the \u201cAmount\u201d field, then select the account you wish to deposit the funds into. Although the deposit is reflected immediately in your account balance, you won\u2019t be able to withdraw or transfer your funds until the hold period has passed.",
      "score": 3.605707883834839
    },
    {
      "question": "How long will the hold period last?",
      "answer": "Canada Post will validate your identity based on the information you provided for your EQ Bank account application. Although the deposit is reflected immediately in your account balance, you won\u2019t be able to withdraw or transfer your funds until the hold period has passed. However, during the hold period, you still earn interest on the deposit amount.",
      "score": 2.1899709701538086
    },
    {
      "question": "During what period do you earn interest on the deposit amount?",
      "answer": "For example, if you make a deposit on a Monday, you can access the funds on the following Tuesday. \u201d Enter the dollar value of the cheque in the \u201cAmount\u201d field, then select the account you wish to deposit the funds into. However, during the hold period, you still earn interest on the deposit amount.",
      "score": 11.729019165039062
    },
    {
      "question": "What policy does Hold Funds Policy cover?",
      "answer": "Generally, EQ Bank hold funds deposited by cheque or Electronic Funds Transfer (EFT) for five business days, beginning after the date of deposit. Although the deposit is reflected immediately in your account balance, you won\u2019t be able to withdraw or transfer your funds until the hold period has passed. For more details, check out our Hold Funds Policy.",
      "score": 0.1230473592877388
    },
    {
      "question": "What bank offers Canadians a digital banking experience?",
      "answer": "EQ Bank launched officially in January 2016 with a commitment to help Canadians get the most out of Canadians money. EQ Bank is the digital arm of Equitable Bank. EQ Bank offers Canadians a digital banking experience.",
      "score": 13.222846984863281
    },
    {
      "question": "When was EQ Bank officially launched?",
      "answer": "EQ Bank launched officially in January 2016 with a commitment to help Canadians get the most out of Canadians money. EQ Bank use the deposits from EQ Bank to furnish EQ Bank residential and commercial loans, and earn interest. Your credit score is not considered when opening an EQ Bank account.",
      "score": 15.713003158569336
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the goal of EQ bank?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. EQ Bank is a trademark of Equitable Bank. EQ Bank is the digital arm of Equitable Bank.",
      "score": 6.029508590698242
    },
    {
      "question": "In what city is EQ Bank located?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. EQ Bank is a trademark of Equitable Bank. Based in Toronto, EQ Bank is a trademark of Equitable Bank.",
      "score": 12.510210990905762
    },
    {
      "question": "How many employees does Equitable Bank have?",
      "answer": "EQ Bank is a trademark of Equitable Bank. Equitable Bank is a federally regulated Schedule I bank with over 900 employees across Canada. Have a Social Insurance Number",
      "score": 11.52034854888916
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the federally regulated Schedule I bank?",
      "answer": "Equitable Bank, Canada Challenger BankTM, is Canada\u2019s ninth largest independent Schedule I bank. The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Equitable Bank is a federally regulated Schedule I bank with over 900 employees across Canada.",
      "score": 10.259140014648438
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Canada's ninth largest independent Schedule I bank?",
      "answer": "Equitable Bank, Canada Challenger BankTM, is Canada\u2019s ninth largest independent Schedule I bank. Equitable Bank is a federally regulated Schedule I bank with over 900 employees across Canada. Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": 13.086057662963867
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the digital arm of Equitable Bank?",
      "answer": "Equitable Bank is a member of the CDIC. EQ Bank is a trademark of Equitable Bank. EQ Bank is the digital arm of Equitable Bank.",
      "score": 11.908143997192383
    },
    {
      "question": "Where can you learn more?",
      "answer": "Meet All EQ Bank customers province\u2019s age of majority (18 or 19 years old, depending on where you live) You can learn more by visiting www.equitablebank.ca. You can learn more about them here.",
      "score": 13.336071014404297
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the website you can visit to learn more about equitybank?",
      "answer": "\u201d Enter the dollar value of the cheque in the \u201cAmount\u201d field, then select the account you wish to deposit the funds into. You can learn more by visiting www.equitablebank.ca. You can learn more about them here.",
      "score": 13.17384147644043
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a good question?",
      "answer": "We\u2019re always looking for good people! Good question! Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": -5.5553154945373535
    },
    {
      "question": "What do banks typically make money by accepting deposits from customers?",
      "answer": "After all, your money is your money. All EQ Bank customers must: Banks typically make money by accepting deposits from customers, and then providing loans to other customers and earning interest from those loans.",
      "score": 1.3316984176635742
    },
    {
      "question": "What does a bank provide loans to other customers and earn interest from their loans?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. EQ Bank use the deposits from EQ Bank to furnish EQ Bank residential and commercial loans, and earn interest. Banks typically make money by accepting deposits from customers, and then providing loans to other customers and earning interest from those loans.",
      "score": 1.9245632886886597
    },
    {
      "question": "What does EQ Bank use to provide residential and commercial loans?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. EQ Bank use the deposits from EQ Bank to furnish EQ Bank residential and commercial loans, and earn interest. EQ Bank do, however, offer cheap, fast, and easy-to-use international money transfers.",
      "score": 10.740800857543945
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the bank that provides residential loans to EQbank?",
      "answer": "Equitable Bank is a member of the CDIC. EQ Bank use the deposits from EQ Bank to furnish EQ Bank residential and commercial loans, and earn interest. EQ Bank is the digital arm of Equitable Bank.",
      "score": 12.470626831054688
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a branchless bank?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. EQ Bank is a trademark of Equitable Bank. Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": 1.940696120262146
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the Savings Plus Account offer you?",
      "answer": "EQ Bank offer a high-interest savings account (Savings Plus Account), TFSA Savings Account, RSP Savings Account, and GICs (guaranteed investment certificates). As a branchless bank, we\u2019re able to reduce we operating costs, and pass on those savings to you in the form of a great everyday interest rate on the Savings Plus Account. The Savings Plus Account is for personal use only.",
      "score": 10.992471694946289
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the person who is always looking for?",
      "answer": "Equitable Bank is a member of the CDIC. We\u2019re always looking for good people! The Savings Plus Account is for personal use only.",
      "score": 2.8972272872924805
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the latest job posting?",
      "answer": "Check out We latest job postings. The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": -3.632481098175049
    },
    {
      "question": "What is one of the most recent job postings?",
      "answer": "Check out We latest job postings. You\u2019ll need to show one of the following pieces of government-issued photo ID: Most recent Income Tax assessment",
      "score": -1.2736011743545532
    },
    {
      "question": "What is really easy to do?",
      "answer": "It\u2019s really easy! EQ Bank do, however, offer cheap, fast, and easy-to-use international money transfers. Each account\u2019s easy!",
      "score": 6.268439292907715
    },
    {
      "question": "How can you open an account?",
      "answer": "All EQ Bank customers must be Canadian residents in order to open and maintain an account. The Income Tax Act requires all banks to obtain your Social Insurance Number when you open an account that earns interest (this includes the Savings Plus Account and GICs). You can open an account by visiting www.eqbank.ca and applying online.",
      "score": 9.867840766906738
    },
    {
      "question": "What does EQ Bank customers have to do?",
      "answer": "All EQ Bank customers must be Canadian residents in order to open and maintain an account. Have a Social Insurance Number All EQ Bank customers must:",
      "score": 7.8542256355285645
    },
    {
      "question": "What must EQ bank customers do to their customers?",
      "answer": "All EQ Bank customers must be Canadian residents in order to open and maintain an account. Banks typically make money by accepting deposits from customers, and then providing loans to other customers and earning interest from those loans. All EQ Bank customers must:",
      "score": 3.9872968196868896
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the age of all EQ Bank customers?",
      "answer": "Meet All EQ Bank customers province\u2019s age of majority (18 or 19 years old, depending on where you live) EQ Bank is a trademark of Equitable Bank. All EQ Bank customers must:",
      "score": 2.645683765411377
    },
    {
      "question": "How old is a EQ bank customer?",
      "answer": "EQ Bank is a trademark of Equitable Bank. EQ Bank is the digital arm of Equitable Bank. Based in Toronto, EQ Bank is a trademark of Equitable Bank.",
      "score": -8.92032527923584
    },
    {
      "question": "What is your province's age of majority?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Meet All EQ Bank customers province\u2019s age of majority (18 or 19 years old, depending on where you live) Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": 10.215694427490234
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a Social Insurance Number?",
      "answer": "The Income Tax Act requires all banks to obtain your Social Insurance Number when you open an account that earns interest (this includes the Savings Plus Account and GICs). Have a Social Insurance Number Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": 0.4827921390533447
    },
    {
      "question": "What is not available in Quebec?",
      "answer": "Please note: EQ Bank is not available in Quebec. The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": 14.214509963989258
    },
    {
      "question": "What do we do as part of our online identity verification process?",
      "answer": "As part of our online identity verification process, we may ask you to sign in to one of the banks below to validate your identity: As part of our online identity verification process, our do a \u201csoft\u201d credit check\u2014meaning your credit score won\u2019t be affected and won\u2019t be visible to other third parties who view your credit report. As part of our online identity verification process, we conduct a \u201csoft\u201d credit check, which doesn\u2019t affect your personal credit score.",
      "score": 13.152259826660156
    },
    {
      "question": "What does our credit check mean your credit score won\u2019t be affected?",
      "answer": "As part of our online identity verification process, we conduct a \u201csoft\u201d credit check, which doesn\u2019t affect your personal credit score. The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. As part of our online identity verification process, our do a \u201csoft\u201d credit check\u2014meaning your credit score won\u2019t be affected and won\u2019t be visible to other third parties who view your credit report.",
      "score": 5.843673229217529
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the Income Tax Act require all banks to obtain your Social Insurance Number when you open an account that earns interest?",
      "answer": "The Income Tax Act requires all banks to obtain your Social Insurance Number when you open an account that earns interest (this includes the Savings Plus Account and GICs). Have a Social Insurance Number All EQ Bank customers must be Canadian residents in order to open and maintain an account.",
      "score": -2.8681955337524414
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the bank that is required to report the interest you earn each year?",
      "answer": "Banks are required to report the interest you earn each year to the Canada Revenue Agency. EQ Bank is the digital arm of Equitable Bank. However, during the hold period, you still earn interest on the deposit amount.",
      "score": 4.874916076660156
    },
    {
      "question": "Who doesn\u2019t support access to your Savings Plus Account?",
      "answer": "EQ Bank offer a high-interest savings account (Savings Plus Account), TFSA Savings Account, RSP Savings Account, and GICs (guaranteed investment certificates). the Canada Revenue Agency don\u2019t officially support access to your Savings Plus Account through Mint. The Savings Plus Account is for personal use only.",
      "score": 5.77101993560791
    },
    {
      "question": "What agency does not offer business accounts?",
      "answer": "Unfortunately, not at the moment. Unfortunately, the Canada Revenue Agency do not currently offer business accounts. EQ Bank don\u2019t offer foreign exchange or USD accounts at the moment.",
      "score": 15.226950645446777
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the Canada Revenue Agency offer?",
      "answer": "Banks are required to report the interest you earn each year to the Canada Revenue Agency. Unfortunately, the Canada Revenue Agency do not currently offer business accounts. the Canada Revenue Agency don\u2019t officially support access to your Savings Plus Account through Mint.",
      "score": 3.031088352203369
    },
    {
      "question": "The Savings Plus Account is for what purpose?",
      "answer": "EQ Bank offer a high-interest savings account (Savings Plus Account), TFSA Savings Account, RSP Savings Account, and GICs (guaranteed investment certificates). the Canada Revenue Agency don\u2019t officially support access to your Savings Plus Account through Mint. The Savings Plus Account is for personal use only.",
      "score": 14.094624519348145
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the account that is used for personal use?",
      "answer": "Equitable Bank is a member of the CDIC. EQ Bank is the digital arm of Equitable Bank. The Savings Plus Account is for personal use only.",
      "score": 11.462177276611328
    },
    {
      "question": "How can you continue to access your existing account while traveling outside of Canada?",
      "answer": "You can continue to access your existing account while travelling outside of Canada. For example, if you make a deposit on a Monday, you can access the funds on the following Tuesday. the Canada Revenue Agency don\u2019t officially support access to your Savings Plus Account through Mint.",
      "score": 0.8680959939956665
    },
    {
      "question": "What must EQ Bank account holders be?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. However, all EQ Bank account holders must be Canadian residents in order to maintain Canadian residents account. All EQ Bank customers must:",
      "score": 9.841435432434082
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the account holders that must be Canadian residents in order to maintain their account?",
      "answer": "All EQ Bank customers must be Canadian residents in order to open and maintain an account. However, all EQ Bank account holders must be Canadian residents in order to maintain Canadian residents account. The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file.",
      "score": 7.459874153137207
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the credit reporting agency that is unable to verify your identity?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. If we\u2019re unable to verify your identity through TransUnion (a credit reporting agency), you can do so by visiting Canada Post and providing your DSS number. If we\u2019re unable to verify your identity through TransUnion (a credit reporting agency), you can do so by visiting Canada Post.",
      "score": 11.439786911010742
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of a bank branch that has a government-issued photo ID?",
      "answer": "Similar to showing your government-issued photo ID at a bank branch, we\u2019ve partnered with Canada Post to make verifying your identity as quick and convenient as possible. You\u2019ll need to show one of the following pieces of government-issued photo ID: 1 piece of government-issued photo ID",
      "score": -2.3070883750915527
    },
    {
      "question": "What does Canada Post do to verify your identity?",
      "answer": "If we\u2019re unable to verify your identity through TransUnion (a credit reporting agency), you can do so by visiting Canada Post and providing your DSS number. Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?) If we\u2019re unable to verify your identity through TransUnion (a credit reporting agency), you can do so by visiting Canada Post.",
      "score": 5.306441783905029
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the outlet that is closest to you?",
      "answer": "Equitable Bank is a member of the CDIC. The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Find the participating Canada Post outlet\u00a0that\u2019s closest to you.",
      "score": 13.139932632446289
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of outlet does Canada Post have?",
      "answer": "Have a Social Insurance Number Find the participating Canada Post outlet\u00a0that\u2019s closest to you. Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": -0.061478883028030396
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the item that you need to bring?",
      "answer": "You\u2019ll need to show one of the following pieces of government-issued photo ID: \u201d Enter the dollar value of the cheque in the \u201cAmount\u201d field, then select the account you wish to deposit the funds into. You\u2019ll need to bring:",
      "score": 4.546762466430664
    },
    {
      "question": "What are some of the things that need to be brought?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. You\u2019ll need to show one of the following pieces of government-issued photo ID: You\u2019ll need to bring:",
      "score": 1.6027714014053345
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of photo ID does the government issue?",
      "answer": "Provincial or territorial photo ID card You\u2019ll need to show one of the following pieces of government-issued photo ID: 1 piece of government-issued photo ID",
      "score": 5.241828918457031
    },
    {
      "question": "What is one piece of ID?",
      "answer": "You\u2019ll need to show one of the following pieces of government-issued photo ID: 1 piece of government-issued photo ID Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": 0.25762322545051575
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the proof of address document if your photo ID doesn't have your current address?",
      "answer": "1 proof of address document (if your photo ID doesn\u2019t have your current address) If your government-issued photo ID doesn\u2019t list your current address, you\u2019ll also need to show a proof of address document, such as: Your government-issued photo ID cannot be expired, and the first and last name, address, and birthdate must be an exact match to the information you provided to us.",
      "score": 8.971108436584473
    },
    {
      "question": "What is your Canada Post DSS number?",
      "answer": "If we\u2019re unable to verify your identity through TransUnion (a credit reporting agency), you can do so by visiting Canada Post and providing your DSS number. A DSS number (or barcode) is given to Canada Post, so A DSS number (or barcode) can validate your identity based on the information in your application on our behalf. Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": 0.2824205160140991
    },
    {
      "question": "What is my Canada Post DS number and why is it important?",
      "answer": "Your Canada Post DSS number will be emailed to you, but if you can\u2019t find it, feel free to call our Customer Care team. A DSS number (or barcode) is given to Canada Post, so A DSS number (or barcode) can validate your identity based on the information in your application on our behalf. Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": 1.7691549062728882
    },
    {
      "question": "What does Canada Post validate your identity?",
      "answer": "Canada Post will validate your identity based on the information you provided for your EQ Bank account application. A DSS number (or barcode) is given to Canada Post, so A DSS number (or barcode) can validate your identity based on the information in your application on our behalf. Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": 11.247186660766602
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the account that Canada Post will validate?",
      "answer": "Canada Post will validate your identity based on the information you provided for your EQ Bank account application. Find the participating Canada Post outlet\u00a0that\u2019s closest to you. Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": 12.653468132019043
    },
    {
      "question": "What must your government-issued photo ID not be expired?",
      "answer": "You\u2019ll need to show one of the following pieces of government-issued photo ID: 1 piece of government-issued photo ID Your government-issued photo ID cannot be expired, and the first and last name, address, and birthdate must be an exact match to the information you provided to us.",
      "score": 2.9575395584106445
    },
    {
      "question": "What must be an exact match to your information?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Your government-issued photo ID cannot be expired, and the first and last name, address, and birthdate must be an exact match to the information you provided to us. All EQ Bank customers must be Canadian residents in order to open and maintain an account.",
      "score": 12.99050235748291
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the photo ID that you need to show?",
      "answer": "You\u2019ll need to show one of the following pieces of government-issued photo ID: If your government-issued photo ID doesn\u2019t list your current address, you\u2019ll also need to show a proof of address document, such as: Your government-issued photo ID cannot be expired, and the first and last name, address, and birthdate must be an exact match to the information you provided to us.",
      "score": 7.769649028778076
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of photo ID card does the provincial or territorial photo ID have?",
      "answer": "1 proof of address document (if your photo ID doesn\u2019t have your current address) Provincial or territorial photo ID card 1 piece of government-issued photo ID",
      "score": -0.04000330716371536
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Canadian Secure Certificate of Indian Status?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Equitable Bank is a member of the CDIC. Canadian Secure Certificate of Indian Status",
      "score": -5.0340776443481445
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Canadian permanent resident card?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Canadian permanent resident card Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": -1.2005023956298828
    },
    {
      "question": "What does a government-issued photo ID not list your current address?",
      "answer": "1 proof of address document (if your photo ID doesn\u2019t have your current address) If your government-issued photo ID doesn\u2019t list your current address, you\u2019ll also need to show a proof of address document, such as: 1 piece of government-issued photo ID",
      "score": 6.310848236083984
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a proof of address document that you need to show?",
      "answer": "1 proof of address document (if your photo ID doesn\u2019t have your current address) You\u2019ll need to show one of the following pieces of government-issued photo ID: If your government-issued photo ID doesn\u2019t list your current address, you\u2019ll also need to show a proof of address document, such as:",
      "score": 5.579505920410156
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a recent utility bill?",
      "answer": "Recent utility bill (residential telephone, cable TV, public utilities commission, hydro, gas, or water) Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?) Most recent Income Tax assessment",
      "score": 10.228458404541016
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of television does a utility bill require?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Recent utility bill (residential telephone, cable TV, public utilities commission, hydro, gas, or water) Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": 9.558891296386719
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the term for Residential Lease, Residential Mortgage Statement or Agreement, Rental Agreement Lease, Agreement of Purchase and Sale?",
      "answer": "EQ Bank use the deposits from EQ Bank to furnish EQ Bank residential and commercial loans, and earn interest. Residential Lease, Residential Mortgage Statement or Agreement, Rental Agreement Lease, Agreement of Purchase and Sale Statement of Old Age Security (T4A) or Statement of Canada Pension Plan Benefits (T4AP)",
      "score": 0.19300371408462524
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a school, college, or university report card or transcript?",
      "answer": "Provincial or territorial photo ID card School, College, or University Report Card or Transcript Canadian permanent resident card",
      "score": -0.21894648671150208
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an example of a college report card?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. School, College, or University Report Card or Transcript An Online Consumer Disclosure is a detailed report of all the information on your credit file, and serves as a way for you to check the data as reported to TransUnion.",
      "score": 1.285773515701294
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Canadian Child Tax Benefit Statement?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Canada Child Tax Benefit statement Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": -5.949456214904785
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the most recent income tax assessment?",
      "answer": "The Income Tax Act requires all banks to obtain your Social Insurance Number when you open an account that earns interest (this includes the Savings Plus Account and GICs). The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Most recent Income Tax assessment",
      "score": -5.111171722412109
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a Government cheque or Government cheque stub?",
      "answer": "Government cheque or Government cheque stub with individual\u2019s name and address 1 piece of government-issued photo ID Click on \u201cSet up Direct Deposit,\u201d then \u201cDownload void cheque.",
      "score": 5.273943901062012
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of a government cheque?",
      "answer": "Take a photo of both the front and back of the cheque, then click \u201cDeposit. Government cheque or Government cheque stub with individual\u2019s name and address \u201d Enter the dollar value of the cheque in the \u201cAmount\u201d field, then select the account you wish to deposit the funds into.",
      "score": 4.184377670288086
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is an individual's name?",
      "answer": "Government cheque or Government cheque stub with individual\u2019s name and address For example, you\u2019re covered for up to $100,000 combined across your individual Savings Plus Account, EQ Bank GICs, and any deposits in your name that you have with Equitable Bank. Your credit score is not considered when opening an EQ Bank account.",
      "score": -2.768160581588745
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Statement of Employment Insurance Benefits?",
      "answer": "Statement of Employment Insurance Benefits Statement of Old Age Security (T4A) or Statement of Canada Pension Plan Benefits (T4AP) Statement of Benefits from Provincial Workplace Safety or Insurance Board",
      "score": -2.868753671646118
    },
    {
      "question": "What is paid (T4E)?",
      "answer": "Paid (T4E) The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": -8.26805305480957
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Canada's Pension Plan Statement of Contributions?",
      "answer": "Canada Pension Plan Statement of Contributions/Quebec Pension Plan Statement of Participation Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?) Statement of Old Age Security (T4A) or Statement of Canada Pension Plan Benefits (T4AP)",
      "score": 1.8500758409500122
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Quebec pension plan Statement of Participation?",
      "answer": "Canada Pension Plan Statement of Contributions/Quebec Pension Plan Statement of Participation Statement of Old Age Security (T4A) or Statement of Canada Pension Plan Benefits (T4AP) Please note: EQ Bank is not available in Quebec.",
      "score": -2.9059479236602783
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Statement of Benefits from Provincial Workplace Safety or Insurance Board?",
      "answer": "Statement of Employment Insurance Benefits Statement of Direct Deposit for Provincial Works or Provincial Disability Support Program Statement of Benefits from Provincial Workplace Safety or Insurance Board",
      "score": -1.1373149156570435
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Statement of Direct Deposit for Provincial Works or Provincial Disability Support Program?",
      "answer": "Provincial or territorial photo ID card Statement of Direct Deposit for Provincial Works or Provincial Disability Support Program Statement of Benefits from Provincial Workplace Safety or Insurance Board",
      "score": -5.884069442749023
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Attestation of Residence issued by the responsible authorities?",
      "answer": "Equitable Bank is a member of the CDIC. \u201d Enter the dollar value of the cheque in the \u201cAmount\u201d field, then select the account you wish to deposit the funds into. Attestation of Residence issued by the responsible authorities (shelters, soup kitchens, student/senior residence, long term care facilities, Aboriginal reserves, work camps)",
      "score": 9.659839630126953
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a student/senior residence issued by?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Attestation of Residence issued by the responsible authorities (shelters, soup kitchens, student/senior residence, long term care facilities, Aboriginal reserves, work camps) Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": 4.437442779541016
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the term for the Statement of Old Age Security?",
      "answer": "Meet All EQ Bank customers province\u2019s age of majority (18 or 19 years old, depending on where you live) The Savings Plus Account is for personal use only. Statement of Old Age Security (T4A) or Statement of Canada Pension Plan Benefits (T4AP)",
      "score": 10.319171905517578
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the term \"T4A\" mean?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Attestation of Residence issued by the responsible authorities (shelters, soup kitchens, student/senior residence, long term care facilities, Aboriginal reserves, work camps) Statement of Old Age Security (T4A) or Statement of Canada Pension Plan Benefits (T4AP)",
      "score": 16.196508407592773
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the name of the statement of old age security?",
      "answer": "Equitable Bank is a member of the CDIC. Meet All EQ Bank customers province\u2019s age of majority (18 or 19 years old, depending on where you live) Statement of Old Age Security (T4A) or Statement of Canada Pension Plan Benefits (T4AP)",
      "score": 7.969570159912109
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the credit reporting agency that can verify your identity?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. If we\u2019re unable to verify your identity through TransUnion (a credit reporting agency), you can do so by visiting Canada Post and providing your DSS number. If we\u2019re unable to verify your identity through TransUnion (a credit reporting agency), you can do so by visiting Canada Post.",
      "score": 12.108566284179688
    },
    {
      "question": "What does TransUnion do if you don't have a DSS?",
      "answer": "Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?) If we\u2019re unable to verify your identity through TransUnion (a credit reporting agency), you can do so by visiting Canada Post. If we\u2019re unable to verify your identity through TransUnion (a credit reporting agency), you can do so by visiting Canada Post and providing your DSS number.",
      "score": 0.300331711769104
    },
    {
      "question": "What is given to Canada Post?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. A DSS number (or barcode) is given to Canada Post, so A DSS number (or barcode) can validate your identity based on the information in your application on our behalf. Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": 9.098224639892578
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a DSS number?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. A DSS number (or barcode) is given to Canada Post, so A DSS number (or barcode) can validate your identity based on the information in your application on our behalf. Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": 7.44477653503418
    },
    {
      "question": "Who can validate your identity based on information in your application?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Canada Post will validate your identity based on the information you provided for your EQ Bank account application. A DSS number (or barcode) is given to Canada Post, so A DSS number (or barcode) can validate your identity based on the information in your application on our behalf.",
      "score": 12.339654922485352
    },
    {
      "question": "What is your DSS number sent to you?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. A DSS number (or barcode) is given to Canada Post, so A DSS number (or barcode) can validate your identity based on the information in your application on our behalf. Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": 0.45446720719337463
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you need to do if you can't find it?",
      "answer": "If you do not bank with any of the companies listed above, you can simply skip this step. Your Canada Post DSS number will be emailed to you, but if you can\u2019t find it, feel free to call our Customer Care team. You\u2019ll need to bring:",
      "score": 8.633289337158203
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you call our Customer Care team?",
      "answer": "our do, and thanks for wanting to tell others about our! Your Canada Post DSS number will be emailed to you, but if you can\u2019t find it, feel free to call our Customer Care team. As part of our online identity verification process, our do a \u201csoft\u201d credit check\u2014meaning your credit score won\u2019t be affected and won\u2019t be visible to other third parties who view your credit report.",
      "score": 2.158271312713623
    },
    {
      "question": "How do we ask you to sign in to a bank to validate your identity?",
      "answer": "As part of our online identity verification process, we may ask you to sign in to one of the banks below to validate your identity: Simply sign in to your account using the EQ Bank mobile app. Sign in to EQ Bank and, from the dashboard, click on your savings accounts.",
      "score": 8.366177558898926
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the bank that can be used to verify your identity in order to verify it?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. If we\u2019re unable to verify your identity through TransUnion (a credit reporting agency), you can do so by visiting Canada Post and providing your DSS number. If we\u2019re unable to verify your identity through TransUnion (a credit reporting agency), you can do so by visiting Canada Post.",
      "score": 11.458540916442871
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the company that does not have a bank account?",
      "answer": "Equitable Bank is a member of the CDIC. EQ Bank is the digital arm of Equitable Bank. For example, you\u2019re covered for up to $100,000 combined across your individual Savings Plus Account, EQ Bank GICs, and any deposits in your name that you have with Equitable Bank.",
      "score": 2.5315706729888916
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a detailed report of all the information on your credit file?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. An Online Consumer Disclosure is a detailed report of all the information on your credit file, and serves as a way for you to check the data as reported to TransUnion. After all, your money is your money.",
      "score": 15.505455017089844
    },
    {
      "question": "What does an Online Consumer Disclosure serve as?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. You can open an account by visiting www.eqbank.ca and applying online. An Online Consumer Disclosure is a detailed report of all the information on your credit file, and serves as a way for you to check the data as reported to TransUnion.",
      "score": 10.424880981445312
    },
    {
      "question": "What must the information you provide in your EQ Bank application match?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Canada Post will validate your identity based on the information you provided for your EQ Bank account application. All EQ Bank customers must:",
      "score": 12.01536750793457
    },
    {
      "question": "What must be a match to the information on your TransUnion credit file?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Your government-issued photo ID cannot be expired, and the first and last name, address, and birthdate must be an exact match to the information you provided to us. An Online Consumer Disclosure is a detailed report of all the information on your credit file, and serves as a way for you to check the data as reported to TransUnion.",
      "score": 7.696833610534668
    },
    {
      "question": "What does EQ Bank deal with?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. EQ Bank use the deposits from EQ Bank to furnish EQ Bank residential and commercial loans, and earn interest. EQ Bank deals with Canadian currency only.",
      "score": 11.107276916503906
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the only way EQ bank deals with Canadian currency?",
      "answer": "EQ Bank is a trademark of Equitable Bank. The Savings Plus Account is for personal use only. EQ Bank deals with Canadian currency only.",
      "score": -3.171934127807617
    },
    {
      "question": "What does EQ Bank offer at the moment?",
      "answer": "Unfortunately, not at the moment. The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. EQ Bank don\u2019t offer foreign exchange or USD accounts at the moment.",
      "score": 2.2611608505249023
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the bank that does not offer foreign exchange or USD accounts?",
      "answer": "EQ Bank is the digital arm of Equitable Bank. Unfortunately, the Canada Revenue Agency do not currently offer business accounts. EQ Bank don\u2019t offer foreign exchange or USD accounts at the moment.",
      "score": 14.633535385131836
    },
    {
      "question": "What does EQ Bank offer cheap, fast, and easy to use international money transfers?",
      "answer": "EQ Bank do, however, offer cheap, fast, and easy-to-use international money transfers. EQ Bank use the deposits from EQ Bank to furnish EQ Bank residential and commercial loans, and earn interest. After all, your money is your money.",
      "score": -5.431509494781494
    },
    {
      "question": "What can you learn more about them here?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. You can learn more by visiting www.equitablebank.ca. You can learn more about them here.",
      "score": 7.309209823608398
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the high-interest savings account offered by EQ Bank?",
      "answer": "EQ Bank offer a high-interest savings account (Savings Plus Account), TFSA Savings Account, RSP Savings Account, and GICs (guaranteed investment certificates). EQ Bank is a trademark of Equitable Bank. EQ Bank is the digital arm of Equitable Bank.",
      "score": 17.40376091003418
    },
    {
      "question": "What is TFSA Savings Account?",
      "answer": "EQ Bank offer a high-interest savings account (Savings Plus Account), TFSA Savings Account, RSP Savings Account, and GICs (guaranteed investment certificates). Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?) The Savings Plus Account is for personal use only.",
      "score": 6.045344352722168
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the cause of the problem?",
      "answer": "Equitable Bank is a member of the CDIC. Take a photo of both the front and back of the cheque, then click \u201cDeposit. \u201d Enter the dollar value of the cheque in the \u201cAmount\u201d field, then select the account you wish to deposit the funds into.",
      "score": -3.1104464530944824
    },
    {
      "question": "What does this cause?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. If you do not bank with any of the companies listed above, you can simply skip this step. Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": -1.6083252429962158
    },
    {
      "question": "Who must be a Canadian resident to open and maintain a EQ Bank account?",
      "answer": "All EQ Bank customers must be Canadian residents in order to open and maintain an account. However, all EQ Bank account holders must be Canadian residents in order to maintain Canadian residents account. Canadian permanent resident card",
      "score": 4.1423468589782715
    },
    {
      "question": "What does a \u201csoft\u201d credit check do?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. As part of our online identity verification process, our do a \u201csoft\u201d credit check\u2014meaning your credit score won\u2019t be affected and won\u2019t be visible to other third parties who view your credit report. As part of our online identity verification process, we conduct a \u201csoft\u201d credit check, which doesn\u2019t affect your personal credit score.",
      "score": 16.117977142333984
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a part of our online identity verification process?",
      "answer": "As part of our online identity verification process, we may ask you to sign in to one of the banks below to validate your identity: As part of our online identity verification process, our do a \u201csoft\u201d credit check\u2014meaning your credit score won\u2019t be affected and won\u2019t be visible to other third parties who view your credit report. As part of our online identity verification process, we conduct a \u201csoft\u201d credit check, which doesn\u2019t affect your personal credit score.",
      "score": 13.4308443069458
    },
    {
      "question": "What is your credit score not considered when opening a EQ Bank account?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Your credit score is not considered when opening an EQ Bank account. Please note: EQ Bank is not available in Quebec.",
      "score": -0.8681636452674866
    },
    {
      "question": "What do we do and thanks for wanting to tell others about our do?",
      "answer": "EQ Bank do, however, offer cheap, fast, and easy-to-use international money transfers. If we\u2019re unable to verify your identity through TransUnion (a credit reporting agency), you can do so by visiting Canada Post. our do, and thanks for wanting to tell others about our!",
      "score": -0.29815250635147095
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you need to share with a friend?",
      "answer": "If you do not bank with any of the companies listed above, you can simply skip this step. To share your referral link, sign in and click on \"Refer a friend.\" You\u2019ll need to bring:",
      "score": 8.178315162658691
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the link that you want to share?",
      "answer": "\u201d Enter the dollar value of the cheque in the \u201cAmount\u201d field, then select the account you wish to deposit the funds into. To share your referral link, sign in and click on \"Refer a friend.\" Find the participating Canada Post outlet\u00a0that\u2019s closest to you.",
      "score": 9.041915893554688
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you sign up to EQ Bank?",
      "answer": "For example, you\u2019re covered for up to $100,000 combined across your individual Savings Plus Account, EQ Bank GICs, and any deposits in your name that you have with Equitable Bank. Simply sign in to your account using the EQ Bank mobile app. Sign in to EQ Bank and, from the dashboard, click on your savings accounts.",
      "score": 11.046833992004395
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of your account that you can click on from the dashboard?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. For example, if you make a deposit on a Monday, you can access the funds on the following Tuesday. Sign in to EQ Bank and, from the dashboard, click on your savings accounts.",
      "score": 11.657149314880371
    },
    {
      "question": "How many numbers does each account have?",
      "answer": "Have a Social Insurance Number Each account has a unique nine-digit number associated with Each account. Each account\u2019s easy!",
      "score": 10.280176162719727
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the unique number of each account?",
      "answer": "Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?) Each account has a unique nine-digit number associated with Each account. Each account\u2019s easy!",
      "score": 10.234498977661133
    },
    {
      "question": "What does each account have?",
      "answer": "Have a Social Insurance Number Each account has a unique nine-digit number associated with Each account. Each account\u2019s easy!",
      "score": 9.310945510864258
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of a simple account?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Equitable Bank is a member of the CDIC. Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": 5.130884170532227
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you sign up to your account?",
      "answer": "For example, you\u2019re covered for up to $100,000 combined across your individual Savings Plus Account, EQ Bank GICs, and any deposits in your name that you have with Equitable Bank. Simply sign in to your account using the EQ Bank mobile app. Sign in to EQ Bank and, from the dashboard, click on your savings accounts.",
      "score": 11.574392318725586
    },
    {
      "question": "What app does EQ Bank use?",
      "answer": "EQ Bank do, however, offer cheap, fast, and easy-to-use international money transfers. EQ Bank use the deposits from EQ Bank to furnish EQ Bank residential and commercial loans, and earn interest. Simply sign in to your account using the EQ Bank mobile app.",
      "score": 4.928919315338135
    },
    {
      "question": "In the bottom right corner, click on what?",
      "answer": "Sign in to EQ Bank and, from the dashboard, click on your savings accounts. Using the EQ Bank mobile app, sign in to your account, then click on the navigation menu in the top right corner. In the bottom right corner, click on \u201cDeposit.",
      "score": 11.031423568725586
    },
    {
      "question": "In what field is the dollar value of the cheque entered?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Take a photo of both the front and back of the cheque, then click \u201cDeposit. \u201d Enter the dollar value of the cheque in the \u201cAmount\u201d field, then select the account you wish to deposit the funds into.",
      "score": 10.566411972045898
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the account you wish to deposit the funds into?",
      "answer": "For example, if you make a deposit on a Monday, you can access the funds on the following Tuesday. \u201d Enter the dollar value of the cheque in the \u201cAmount\u201d field, then select the account you wish to deposit the funds into. Although the deposit is reflected immediately in your account balance, you won\u2019t be able to withdraw or transfer your funds until the hold period has passed.",
      "score": -0.4414694905281067
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the photo taken from the front and back of the cheque?",
      "answer": "Equitable Bank is a member of the CDIC. Take a photo of both the front and back of the cheque, then click \u201cDeposit. \u201d Enter the dollar value of the cheque in the \u201cAmount\u201d field, then select the account you wish to deposit the funds into.",
      "score": 3.2517480850219727
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the question that prompted the question?",
      "answer": "Equitable Bank is a member of the CDIC. \u201d Enter the dollar value of the cheque in the \u201cAmount\u201d field, then select the account you wish to deposit the funds into. Good question!",
      "score": -5.971521377563477
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the question ask about the question of a person?",
      "answer": "As part of our online identity verification process, we may ask you to sign in to one of the banks below to validate your identity: \u201d Enter the dollar value of the cheque in the \u201cAmount\u201d field, then select the account you wish to deposit the funds into. Good question!",
      "score": -1.041365146636963
    },
    {
      "question": "What is zero monthly banking fees?",
      "answer": "We\u2019re all about zero monthly banking fees! We don\u2019t charge account fees, fees for sending or receiving Interac e-Transfers\u00ae, fees for bill payments, overdraft fees, or dormant account fees. Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": -3.494105815887451
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the minimum monthly banking fee?",
      "answer": "The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. We\u2019re all about zero monthly banking fees! Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": 6.6937336921691895
    },
    {
      "question": "What do we charge for sending or receiving Interac e-Transfers\u00ae?",
      "answer": "EQ Bank do, however, offer cheap, fast, and easy-to-use international money transfers. Check out the full list of fees we don\u2019t charge. We don\u2019t charge account fees, fees for sending or receiving Interac e-Transfers\u00ae, fees for bill payments, overdraft fees, or dormant account fees.",
      "score": 0.43613120913505554
    },
    {
      "question": "What are fees for overdraft fees?",
      "answer": "We\u2019re all about zero monthly banking fees! Check out the full list of fees we don\u2019t charge. We don\u2019t charge account fees, fees for sending or receiving Interac e-Transfers\u00ae, fees for bill payments, overdraft fees, or dormant account fees.",
      "score": 3.6093907356262207
    },
    {
      "question": "What is your money?",
      "answer": "After all, your money is your money. The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": 6.416665554046631
    },
    {
      "question": "What does your money mean?",
      "answer": "After all, your money is your money. The information you provide in your EQ Bank application must be an exact match to what is on your TransUnion credit file. Your Canada Post DSS number (see What is my Canada Post DSS number and why is it important?)",
      "score": 8.3836030960083
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the full list of fees we don\u2019t charge?",
      "answer": "We\u2019re all about zero monthly banking fees! Check out the full list of fees we don\u2019t charge. We don\u2019t charge account fees, fees for sending or receiving Interac e-Transfers\u00ae, fees for bill payments, overdraft fees, or dormant account fees.",
      "score": 7.345880031585693
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you sign in to your account?",
      "answer": "Simply sign in to your account using the EQ Bank mobile app. Sign in to EQ Bank and, from the dashboard, click on your savings accounts. Using the EQ Bank mobile app, sign in to your account, then click on the navigation menu in the top right corner.",
      "score": 11.834888458251953
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the navigation menu in the top right corner of the app?",
      "answer": "\u201d Enter the dollar value of the cheque in the \u201cAmount\u201d field, then select the account you wish to deposit the funds into. Using the EQ Bank mobile app, sign in to your account, then click on the navigation menu in the top right corner. In the bottom right corner, click on \u201cDeposit.",
      "score": -2.0428123474121094
    },
    {
      "question": "When you click on \"Set up Direct Deposit,\" then \"Download void cheque?\"",
      "answer": "Take a photo of both the front and back of the cheque, then click \u201cDeposit. Click on \u201cSet up Direct Deposit,\u201d then \u201cDownload void cheque. In the bottom right corner, click on \u201cDeposit.",
      "score": -9.482810974121094
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the question that prompted the question?",
      "answer": "Equitable Bank is a member of the CDIC. \u201d Enter the dollar value of the cheque in the \u201cAmount\u201d field, then select the account you wish to deposit the funds into. Good question!",
      "score": -5.971521377563477
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the question ask about the question of a person?",
      "answer": "As part of our online identity verification process, we may ask you to sign in to one of the banks below to validate your identity: \u201d Enter the dollar value of the cheque in the \u201cAmount\u201d field, then select the account you wish to deposit the funds into. Good question!",
      "score": -1.041365146636963
    }
  ]
}